<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thales Bertaglia</title><link>https://thalesbertaglia.com/</link><description>Recent content on Thales Bertaglia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-UK</language><copyright>Copyright © 2021, Thales Bertaglia.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thalesbertaglia.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://thalesbertaglia.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thalesbertaglia.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://thalesbertaglia.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thalesbertaglia.com/about/</guid><description>about me I am a PhD Candidate at Maastricht University, working jointly with the Institute of Data Science and Studio Europa. My research focuses on using NLP and other computational methods to understand the influence of content creators and content monetisation on social media. I am also part of the Computational Social Media research group. I am supervised by Catalina Goanta, Mathieu Segers, and Michel Dumontier.
 From Jun/2019 to Dec/2019 I was an Applied Data Scientist intern at Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Search Technology Center (Munich).</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://thalesbertaglia.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thalesbertaglia.com/projects/</guid><description>projects For code, check out my GitHub page
Business Model Prevalence in Influencer Marketing on Instagram: This research project brings together expertise from Natural Language Processing (NLP) and European Consumer Law and aims to make a gap-filling contribution focused on determining which particular influencer marketing business models can be identified on social media, and how influencers use them.
Abusive Language on YouTube: a dataset of YouTube comments in English extracted from videos on different controversial topics and labelled by Law students.</description></item></channel></rss>